Hello.
This is Rei Oizono from Fukura High School 46.
Yu Mura and Rika Ishimori
The three of us came to play basketball today.
Hi!
Gymnasium
It's a gymnasium.
We're... experienced basketball players.
How long have you each been playing?
I've been playing basketball for seven years, from the third grade to the ninth grade.
That's great.
I was in junior high for three years.
Three years of junior high.
We're the same.
I was in the club for three years.
And eventually, I'd like to have these three plus
I'd like to make a Sakurazaka basketball team.
I'd like to form the Sakurazaka basketball team.
Sakurazaka basketball team.
Sakurazaka Basketball Club
Basketball club
Basketball team
I'd like to create a basketball team!
Let's have a try!
If you have any favorite moves that you used to be good at when you were a player...
What was your position?
Oh, position?
I was a guard.
Maybe a lot.
I was that too.
Why were you on the shooting range, like this, carrying the ball?
Cool.
And you, Mika?
I'm a guard and a forward.
I'm a center forward. Sometimes I play center.
I also hit from the outside. It's a good split. You have a good balance.
Do you have different strengths?
I'll start with my seniors.
I don't use the board against this ring.
I was good at hitting from 0 degrees.
I was really good at it back then.
It's true, the center ball...
From the side.
Thank you.
Miracle.
This year.
That was a guard.
I've been working on getting him out of this area.
I'd cut into him.
Or hit a layup.
I'll see what I can do.
Oh, wait a minute.
What?
Wait a minute.
Let me try again.
Hint, hint.
Wow, nice, nice.
I'm gonna...
You know...
I didn't like crowds.
I was scared.
I've been hitting 3-pointers.
You think you can do it?
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh!
Wow.
That's cool.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
That's amazing.
That's great.
I was practicing my 3-point.
Cool.
I'll try it.
Ooh.
Oh, nice.
Yay!
Beautiful
Yum!
Ooh!
cool!
so cool!
I got it, I got it.
This ball
On the ground.
What was that all about?
One more time through the hole.
Pimemaru.
I couldn't get it down.
The gymnastics.
His feet were spinning.
Once and hd
I don't know.
Okay, I'll do it.
That's cool.
I don't know.
This, this, this.
I want to do this.
It's done.
Can you do it?
I got it.
This, this, this.
I think I can do it.
Get up.
Ninety-nine.
This, this, this.
It's done.
I got a lot of this.
It took a lot of work.
What's this?
I did it! I did it!
I miss these.
We used to have one like this, didn't we?
Yay! Yay!
I love this one.
I thought, "Hurry up and get it over with.
I miss these
This is great
I can't do it!
Fast, fast, fast.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
It's real.
During the game.
Have you ever used one of these?
No, no, no, no, no.
Do guards use this?
I used to do the backflip a lot.
Wow.
That's a high level.
It's a high level.
Oh, my God.
My first time!
Oh, wow!
Oh, it's gone.
That's cool.
Trap Trap Trap
That's awesome!
I can use that.
Okay, let's have a little showdown.
I'd like to try a little showdown.
There's three of us.
One against two.
Two.
Offense?
One of us is going to defend.
What are we going to do, tits?
Let's see.
Let's understand.
I'll play defense.
Fence.
I'm going in.
You want to go around?
I'll do it.
Here we go.
Yes, sir.
We've got him.
Two minutes.
I'll do it.
Yes, sir.
Here.
Head
Ew.
Ugh.
Head
I've been living on this kind of speed.
I've always been
I've always been an agile guy.
He pulled it out like this.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
You ready?
Can you do it?
That's how you pull it out.
I see.
Yes!
Nice!
That's good.
That's great.
I dribble.
I've never done that in my life.
I've never dribbled in my life.
I can walk.
Walk.
To walk.
I tried walking.
Wow!
That looks like a basketball team!
Looks like a basketball team
Dribbling
The basketball-ish side of me.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, wait.
Running to the passer?
Maybe even run behind the person who passed you.
You're right, I would.
Memorial.
That's fun!
It's like a great basketball game!
Queen.
Ohhhh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh! Oh!
Ahh!
ah ah ah ah
ah
I knew
Hmm.
I'm going to do a free throw game with the three of us, so I'd like to do it.
Since we're here, I think it would be great if the three of us could do free throws together.
Let's do it!
All three of us.
Three in a row.
If you can't make it
Punishment game.
Yay!
I got it.
What would you like to see in a penalty game?
Have you ever had to pay a penalty specific to your size? Until now.
Yeah.
Well, we've been known to...
If there's something like that...
Our advisor would get the anti-magic ready.
What do you call it?
Ahhh...
Plank was the punishment.
It was more like a punishment.
It was like a Barbie, like a derby.
Bar. Bar.
I might have done it.
Like a derby.
Yes, like that.
Like a... Like a...
Like a bar.
That sounds like a lot of work.
It's got to be a Barbie.
Sure, can I make it a Barbie then?
Wow, I wonder how many strokes I'll have to do.
Wow.
I missed it.
Three from the first one in.
I'll go first.
Here you go.
Hold on.
It's okay. It's okay.
Don't go straight.
If Yoo-chan comes in, we'll ask Yoo-chan.
Eleven.
Johis
Oh no, I didn't decide on this one.
What should we do?
Oh, no.
I know, I know, I know.
I'll make it ten.
Ten.
I don't know if I can do it.
Like this.
Stretch it out.
Stretch, close, close, jump.
Tight.
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Tight, tight, tight.
Wait a minute, this is bad.
Let's make it like five times next time.
Let's make it five times.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, my God.
I think we're done.
Okay, okay.
It's kind of routine.
Was it? Free throws.
There were.
One or two.
Oh, I'm always in the same boat.
Dribbling.
I'm a dribbling kind of guy.
Oh, baby.
Thank you.
Yuu aru?
I'll give you one hand.
And then I hit it three times.
I do that.
That could be bad.
Wow, that's amazing.
Oh, my God.
Does that mean it's started?
It means it's started.
Oh, please.
Oh, no.
We don't have a choice.
Five.
One. - One.
Two.
Three. - Four.
Four.
Five.
Oh, this is a little bad.
Oh, it's a little bad
Oh, it's a little bit bad
Oh, a little bit bad.
Okay, so even if the three of us don't do it in a row...
I'll end it when we're done.
I guess we're done.
Sure thing.
See you in the next video.
No.
Then let's do that.
Deal.
Let's go in for now.
Mika, I'm coming in.
I'm so disconnected.
Wait, wait, wait.
That's good.
I got it!
I'm in.
I'm in. I'm in. I'm in.
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
I got it!
You did it!
We did it!
I think this is the end of the first Sakurazaka Basketball Club
I think I'll end here.
It was fun!
It was really a club activity, wasn't it?
I really remember now!
It was fun, last week
And the youth of summer
In order to do it as a club activity in the future
I'd like to make a team.
If you're scouting for a team...
Do you think of Rika?
Oh, Rika-chan.
Nagi-chan.
Nagi-chan from the third term.
Nagi's voice is important in basketball.
How is her voice?
And she's tall, too.
She's tall, too.
Also, she's like this.
Oh, I have an image of excellent mobility.
I don't know...
He's also tall, and, you know, he's like...
I think he can do it.
He might be a strong candidate.
Very strong.
Right?
I'm inviting him to join us.
The captain of this team.
I've already decided who I want to go with today.
I've decided, too.
Let's go, Ryutachi-yan.
You were so cool.
He was cool.
He was so cool.
In his free time, he would reminisce about how he used to do things like this during his club activities.
I thought he was a senior in various knowledge and skills.
Riku-chan is the captain of the club, and I hope you will enjoy the club activities in the future.
If you enjoyed this video, please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
If you liked this video, please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
Cute!
Bye bye!
I'll do my best.
I'm waiting for your comments.
Can I do some cool tricks?
Please do.
I don't know if I can do it.
I'd like to see it.
It's a layup like...
Oh, nice shoot.
That's cool.
Back.
The back.
That's a great back.
Can you do that?
Oh, my God.
Oh, nice shooting.